<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>myzonesoft.com</title>
    <link>https://myzonesoft.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on myzonesoft.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:03:48 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://myzonesoft.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Migration from Wordpress to Hugo and GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://myzonesoft.com/post/getting-started-with-hugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 13:03:48 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myzonesoft.com/post/getting-started-with-hugo/</guid>
      <description>In this post, I have documented all the steps I took to migrate this website from Wordpress to Hugo and host it on GitHub Pages.
Hugo is the world’s fastest static website engine. It is written in Golang.
GitHub Pages provides free hosting space for the static sites.
Installation of Hugo Follow the Hugo documentation on Installing Hugo on Windows.
Given below are same steps from the above article.
Download and Install the Hugo Executable for Windows 10  Go to the Hugo Releases page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://myzonesoft.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myzonesoft.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to myzonesoft.com technical website.
The main purpose of this website is to provide articles related to working on latest technologies, so that we could learn and grow our knowledge together.
This website was initially developed and hosted on the Wordpress.
Now it is generated using Hugo with Mainroad theme and hosted on GitHub Pages.
Read this article, in order to understand more about this interesting journey.
Thanks for reading!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Develop Microservice Application Using Spring Boot and H2 Database</title>
      <link>https://myzonesoft.com/post/microservice-spring-boot-h2-db/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://myzonesoft.com/post/microservice-spring-boot-h2-db/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this article, I will be developing a microservice application using &lt;strong&gt;Java Technology&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Spring Boot Framework&lt;/strong&gt;, which will be the backend and expose all &lt;em&gt;CRUD (Create, Read, Update, Delete) Operations&lt;/em&gt; as the REST APIs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will be using &lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relational Database&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt; known as &lt;strong&gt;H2 Database&lt;/strong&gt;, it is also known as an Embedded Java Database, for persisting(storing) the data.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
